



# BORISLAV IZMESTIEV

WEB DEVELOPER





#### **PROFILE**

I am a web-developer with experience in creating web-sites (HTML, CSS, JS). I like to read articles about Web-Development, train skills in CodeWars and improve my English skills. Also i have interest to learn new technologies. I'm ready for full-time or part-time work.



## SKILLS

#### Skills

HTML5/CSS3, JavaScript Basic, BEM, Mobile First, Pixel-Perfect, Flexbox, Grid, responsive and adaptive, SVG

## Frameworks/Systems

React JS, Material UI, Bootstrap, Visual Studio Code, Webstorm, Git, WordPress, Figma, Avacode, Adobe Photoshop, Zeplin, LESS, SASS (SCSS), Stylus, PUG

### Languages

English pre-intermideate (in progress) Russian



## CONTACTS

City: Moscow

Email: borislavizmestiev@gmail.com









## CAREER SUMMARY



### **Freelance Developer**

January 2021 to present

- Develop sites using various libraries and technologies
- Fix bugs and errors on sites
- Work with ready-made template for WordPress
- Create pages on React (SPA)

## Foreign trade officer

LTD Quasar Diamonds | 2015 to 2021

- Working with clients from India, Israel, Hong Kong, UAE
- Draw up documents and send packages abroad
- Work with government structures

## **EDUCATIONAL TRAINING**



#### IT-Incubator

2020 to 2021

Web-developer (HTML5, CSS3, Grid Layout, Flex, BEM, LESS, SASS, Animation, SVG, adaptability and responsibility, React(Node.js, NPM), Mobile First, Pixel Perfect, Material UI etc.

#### **Krasnogorsky College**

2012 to 2016

Optician - Mechaniker

- Worked on Krasnogorsky Factory 'Zenit' in mechanical workshop
- · Take part in optician expo's

## **Russian Technological University MIREA**

2016 to 2020

Bachelor of optics science

- Worked in university's lab
- Developed optical bench for my final qualifying work